http://www.topseos.com/privacy-policy

topseos Privacy Policy
Chat with us,
powered by LiveChat
Edition:
United States
Popular Countries:
India
All Countries:
View Best Firms For Small Businesses
View rankings of the best companies by category:
View Best Firms For Enterprises
View rankings of the best companies by category:
Apply for Rankings
If you are interested in having your company included on our rankings, click here.
Home »
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Updated: Tuesday, August 27, 2019
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
We may update this Privacy Agreement from time to time as our services change and expand.
THIS SITE CONTAINS LINKS TO OTHER SITES
topseos.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites to which the site links to or which link to the site. By clicking on a link, logo, or other item, please note that you may no longer be on the topseos.com site.
INFORMATION WE GATHER
If you register to buy or sell services using topseos.com, We collect and store information that specifically identifies you or your account (Personally Identifiable Information).
YOUR PUBLIC PROFILE
As part of registration, we collect information which is used to generate a company profile of companies. You will be required to provide some information about your company or business. If you decide to offer a service or a product, potential buyers will look to your company profile to help them decide whether to connect with you or not for such products / services.
REGISTRATION INFORMATION
We use Personally Identifiable Information for our own internal purposes including contacting you via email to inform you about updates to our services and providing you with information relating to e-commerce transactions that you conduct on the site. We reserve the right to disclose your information as required by law. We may additionally provide you with newsletters via email.
HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION
We collect personal information about you as peruse of our site, interact with our customer service representatives, complete online order forms or information request sheets, and provide your information to our sales agents. We may use cookies and pixel tags to track your usage of our websites. We also use online order forms and information request sheets to obtain information from you necessary to process your orders and provide you with requested information.
EMAIL TRANSMISSIONS
We may send email transmissions to our users about various products and services being offered. We may also send requests to users in regards to updating their profiles or providing more complete information about their company. In addition, we may send out promotional messages on behalf of our affiliates regarding their products and services.
All users, unless otherwise unsubscribed from further email transmissions, will receive the promotional and transactional messages via the email address which they used when registering their company profile. In addition, users which opt-in to our email notification system will also be transmitted promotional messages unless they opt-out of communication.
For all opt-out requests, please allow three to five business days for your email to be removed from our system. For requests sent via mail or telephone, please allow additional time for the message to be delivered in order for the opt-out request to be handled.
SECURITY MEASURES
We have created and implemented a variety of encryption and security technologies and procedures to protect information stored in our systems for from unauthorized access. Further, we maintain procedural safeguards that restrict access to your personal and private customer information to our employees who need to know your customer information in order to provide the services that you request from time to time.
ACCESS TO INFORMATION
In the event that you have any concerns or inquiries about the customer information we have collected, or to access your information, please e-mail us at support@topseos.com. We may require the payment of a minimal administrative fee for accessing or copying your information, but will inform you of the anticipated charges and confirm that you want us to proceed before processing your request. If you believe that the customer information about you that we have collected is incomplete or inaccurate, we will correct the information upon verification of the omission or error and that the person requesting the change is the person about whom the customer information relates.
LEGAL DISCLAIMER
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.
Our Partners
Become a Partner
Small Business Rankings
Best SEO Companies
Best PPC Companies
Integrated Search Companies
Reputation Management
Social Media Marketing
topseos.com Everywhere!
Reach us from wherever you are. Get the latest updates fast.
topseos.com.
Use of this website constitutes acceptance of Terms & Conditions |
Privacy Policy |
Legal Disclosure
CONFIRM YOUR IDENTITY
We rely on user reviews and ratings in order to help our buyers.
We take reviews that are attached to a LinkedIn account much more seriously and consider them as legitimate user reviews.
Confirm identity with LinkedIn
Register
Get Your Business Listed
8/10 buyers choose a recommended vendor. Be a part of our list and close more business.
Become a recommended vendor.
Generate more leads.
Increase your conversions.
Control your public image.
Nationwide Exposure
Be recognized as one of the best within your industry Nationwide. Generate qualified leads.
Local / Regional Exposure
Dominate your local presence. Reach local businesses seeking your products and services.
Sign up with Linkedin
Learn More
Frequently Asked Questions
Learn more about your presence on topseos.com. Get answers to common questions.
Ensure your potential customers see the most recent and accurate data about your company.
